Robert R. Simmons Papers
© 2007 University of Connecticut
- Series I: Files, undated, 1991-2006
  - Pending Grants as of 12/6/2006, undated, 2004-2006 (Box 142)
    - Drug Free Communities, Announcements to Towns, 2005 February
    - Connecticut State Homeland Security, Assessment--Municipalities, 2004 February 17
    - COPS COnference call, undated
    - EASTConn, 2006 June 29
    - East Hampton Water, undated
    - Electric Boat Workers, undated
    - Enfield, Drug Free Communities, 2006 March 30
    - EPA Healthy COmmunities, Mail merge to Municipal leaders, 2005 March 31
    - ERASE, 2006 April 4
    - FEMA, Flood Disaster, 2005 October 14-15, 2005 December 16
    - First Step, 2005 August 5
    - Generations Family Health Center, Willimantic, 330 renewal, 2005
    - Generations, 2006 September 29
    - Governors Prevention partnership, undated
    - Grant workshops, 2005 April 13
    - Griswold Airport Property, Madison, undated
    - Grow Jobs CT, 2005 June 17
    - Homeland Security (State), undated
    - HVCC, undated
    - Headstart/EASTConn/TVCCA, undated
    - Hebron Athletic Fields, 2006 February 10
    - Hooker Hotel, Willimantic, 2003 December 17
    - Huntington Homestead, undated
    - Huntington Homestead, Kevin Ring, undated
    - International Coalition for Children and the Environment (ICCE), 2006 June 14
    - LEL Corporation, Charles Liucci, Enfield, undated
    - La Casademi Padre, Chip Chiapperini, undated
    - Long Island Sound Foundation, 2006 January 4
    - Madison, Drug Free Communities, 2005 March 8
    - Madonna Place, Nancy Gentes, 2005 April 27
    - Mansfield, Storrs Center, undated
    - McKinney, Steart B. Wildlife Refuge, Westbrook, undated
    - Medicare events, 2004 January 22
    - Medicare letter, 2006 August 11
    - Muddy Brook Fire Dept., 2005 May 11
    - Museum of Connecticut Glass, Coventry, 2004 September 15
    - National endowment for the Arts announcements, 2005
    - NECCOG meeting, 2003 May 30
    - Network, CT, 2003 January 3
    - New Air Technology, 2005 January 14
    - New London Youth Organization Kids Cafe Capacity building grant, undated
    - New Lond Youth Organization, 2006 May 1
    - New London Brownfields Assessment, 2005 January 6
    - New London housing Authority, undated
    - NECASA Drug Free Communities, 2005 March 30
    - No Child Left Behind, undated
    - North Coventry Fire Department, 2006 March 30
    - Norwich, 2005 May 26
    - Norwich Golf Course Authority, 2002 September 12
    - Occum Park (Norwich Community Development Corporation), 2004 February 11
    - Eugene O'Neill Monte Cristo Cottage, 2004 January 26
    - Pfizer Medicare Drug Coverage, 2005
    - Plainfield InterRoyal Mill, 2005 May 20
    - Prevention Council of Haddam-Killingworth, 2004 December 15
    - Police on Patrol, 2002 September 20
    - President's Family Justice Center Initiative, 2003-2004
    - regional School District 18, Old Lyme/Lyme, 2005 July 21
    - Rose Commons, Vernon, sayebrook Village, E and W, 2006 June 29
    - Rose City Senior Center Prescription Drug Forum, 2003 November 17
    - Save America's Treasures, 2004-2005
    - Scotland Fire Department, 2005 April 15
    - Slater Museum, 2006 March 30
    - Slater Museum, 2006 November 15
    - Stafford Community Owned Discount Store, 2006 January 17
    - Sterling Memorial School, 2005 September 2
    - Thompson Ecumenical Empowerment Group (TEEG), 2006 June 14
    - Tolland-Oakridge Farm, 2005 April 1
    - United Community and Family Services, 2006 July 12
    - UConn School of Nursing, 2005 October 26
    - Willimantic Drug Free Communities, 2005
    - Willimantic Whitewater Partnership, 2004 April 21
    - Willimantic Fire Chief's Switchboard Association, 2005 November 22
    - Willimantic Housing Authority, 2005 October 26
    - Yellow Barn--UConn, 2005 April 11
    - Youth and Family Services of Haddam-Killingworth, 2006 July 11
    - Abundant Life Community Church, 2003 December 17
    - Vernon-Bolton Sewer Project, 2004 May 24
    - Westbrook Dredging, 2005 January 26
  - Defense Issues/International, undated, 2003-2004 (Box 143)
    - Iraq, undated
    - Exchange visitor program, undated
    - Bucks waiting response, undated
    - Saudi Arabia, undated
    - Syria, undated
    - Taiwan, undated
    - Thailand, undated
    - Pakistan, undated
    - Lybia n Jews, undated
    - Korea, undated
    - Israel: H.Res. 479 "Geneva Resolution,", undated
    - American Shipbuilding Association, Congressional Industry workshop, 2003 December
    - Naval Sea Cadet Corps information packet, undated
    - Epocrates, Intuitive solutions for the medical mind, undated
    - Croatian American Association, 14th annual Croatia n days on the Hill, 2004 May
    - Bolduc Machine Works, undated
    - MPRI Ship analytics update, 2004 June 30
    - Global Engineering and Materials, Inc., 2004 October 17
    - NESRPS, Engineering controls, undated
    - Colombia, undated
    - Cuba, undated
    - France, undated
    - Germany, undated
    - Haiti, undated
    - Israel, undated
    - China, undated
    - FY 2007 National Defense Authorization Bill, I-IV, undated
    - United Technologies Corp., undated, 2003
      - Commanche termination
      - George David
      - Marine One
      - 2003 Accomplishments
      - Igor Sikorsky resolution
      - Sikorsky
      - President's dinner Commanche speech, 2003 June 9
    - Constituent letters (2 folders), undated
  - FY 2004 Defense authorization, FY 2005 Defense requests, Appropriations, undated, 2003-2006 (Box 144)
    - FY 2004 Defense authorization, undated
      - I-II
      - Environment/Personnel issues
      - HR 1588 Defense authorization
      - Projection Forces mark
      - SASC
      - Airland mark
      - Chairman's mark
      - Abortion
      - Smith Act amendment
    - FY 2005 Defense requests, undated
      - NDAA mark
      - CSU system
      - Northrup Grumman
      - ADI-Sonarman Earcom
      - Anteon
      - ATK
      - CamelBak
      - Chesapeake Sciences
      - Command Technology
      - Commonwealth Consulting
      - CTANG
      - DDL OMNI Engineering (3 folders)
      - Michael Dillon--EB
      - ADI EBA & D
      - Flight Safety Technologies
      - Fuel Cell Energy
      - General Physics: Net Centric
      - Goodrich
      - Kildare
      - Lithion/Yardney
      - Navy Sea Cadet Corps
      - Northrup Grumman
      - NUFERN
      - Phelps Dodge
      - Purdy
      - Progeny Systems
      - Shock Tube Systems
      - UTC
      - HASC-Dental Bill
      - Subase, NL, Milcon
      - Guidelines for FY 2005 Member requests
      - Memorandum: Earmarks in Appropriations bill, 2004 February 6
      - The Kildare Corp>
      - Interlocks training
    - Appropriations, undated
      - Amistad America
      - Mystic Seaport
      - Quinebaug-Shetucket Heritage Corridor, I-III
      - House Subcommittee on Defense, FY 2006 request forms
      - House Subcommittee on Defense, FY 2007 request forms
  - Appropriations, 2002-2007 (Box 145)
    - Avery Point Lighthouse (2 folders), undated
    - International Children's Conference on the Environment, undated
    - Florence Griswold Museum, undated
    - UConn, undated
    - Sam Kovnat/SDI, undated
    - East Hampton water, undated
    - Mystic Seascape project, undated
    - Letters, undated
    - FY 2006 (2 folders), undated
    - Letters, undated
    - Conference items, undated
    - Master plan, undated
    - Forms, undated
    - Willington Senior housing, undated
    - Norwich ITC funds renewals (earmark 2001), undated
    - By Town, undated
    - Background materials, undated; [2 ff]
    - Dredging feasibility evaluation of Fitchville Pond, Bozrah, CT, undated
    - Unidentified materials, undated
    - NURP Undersea research, undated
    - FY 2007 Appropriations, undated
    - UConn FY 2005 funding requests, undated
    - UConn FY 2006 funding requests, undated
    - FY 2005 Appropriations, undated
    - Est Hampton STAG funds FY 2005, undated
    - Interior FY 2004, undated
    - Interior Appropriations FY 2003, undated
    - VA/HUD Appropriations FY 2004, undated
    - Transportation/Treasury FY 2004, undated
  - Appropriations and Grant files, 2002-2005 (Box 146)
    - FY 2005 Interior appropriations, Conservation amendments, undated
    - Trans-Treasury, undated
    - Appropriations FY 2003--Projects, undated
    - Appropriations FY 2004--Projects, undated
    - Letter copies FY 2005, undated
    - Forms, undated
    - Follow ups, undated
    - Depts. of Veterans Affairs and Housing and Urban Development and Independent Agencies appropriations bill, 2002
    - Dept. of Tranportation and related agencies appropriations bill, 2002
    - Depts. of Tranportation and Treasury and independent agencies appropriations bill, 2004
    - AARP meeting, 2004 June 4
    - AARP meeting, undated
    - ACCESS (DHHS Promoting Healthy marriages), 2003 August 7
    - ACCESS Agency, undated
    - ACCESS Agency (HUD LEAP Grant), 2002 November 18
    - ACCESS Agency, 2004 June 9
    - ACCESS Agency LEAP Grant, 2004
    - ACCESS Agency (State DSS REACH program), 2003 June 24
    - ACCESS Agency--Housing, 2002 December 18
    - ACCESS Agency grants (USDA rural development, HUD), undated
    - Aerospace Components Mfg., ACM grant, 2002
    - Aerospace Components Mfg., DOC Market Development Cooperation program, undated
    - Ames workers DOL grant (Mike Pace), undated
    - Antiquarian and Landmarks Society Hale Homestead (QSHA), 2004 March 30
    - Baltic Fire Co. (2004 Assistance to Firefighters), 2004 April 16
    - Barn Island Wildlife Management area, 2003 September 19
    - Beach Act, 2004 August 19
    - Henry C. Bowen House, Woodstock (SPNEA), 2003 June 4
    - Boys and Girls Club of SE CT, 2003 June 17
    - Bozrah Volunteer Fire Co. (2004 Assistance to Firefighters), 2004 April 12
    - Brownfields (EPA, 2 folders), 2003
    - Bulletproof vest partnership (DOJ, 2 folders), 2003-2004
    - Bungay Fire Brigade (2004 Assistance to Firefighters, 2 folders), 2004 March 30
    - Business Industry Foundation of Middlesex County (DOJ Drug Free Communities support program), 2003 August 15
    - Canterbury Volunteer Fire Co. (FEMA Assistance to Firefighters, 2 folders), 2003-2004
    - Capitol Region Workforce Investment (earmark), 2005
    - Capitol Region COG--West Hartford Fire Department (FEMA, Assistance to Firefighters--HAZMAT Vehicle), undated
    - CARA, 2004 December 1
    - Cedar Island MArina, Clinton, dredging, 2005
    - Center Groton Fire Department (FEMA Assistance to Firefighters), 2003 April
    - Chesterfield Fire Co. (FEMA), 2003 May 9
    - Chester Hose Co., 2004 April 11
    - Child and Family Agency of SE CT, New London Region, undated
    - Children Adoption Resouce Association (CARA), 2003 March 26
    - Children's Museum Extension request, 2003 June 24
    - Children's Trust Fund--CDC grant, 2002 August 26
    - Clinton Drug Free Communities, 2001-2004
    - The Connection, Inc., 2004 June 16
    - CT Academy for Education, 2004 August 12
    - CT Agricultural Business Cluster (Value added agricultural products marketing development grant, 2 folders), undated, 2003
    - CT Children and Family Center, New Haven County, 2003 September 29
    - CT Council on Developmental Disabilities, 2003 July 7
    - State of CT, Pre-disaster Mitigation, 2003 August 14
    - State of CT, 2005
    - Connecticut College, New London (2 folders), 2003
    - State of CT, Historic Preservation grant, 2003 April 1
    - State of CT, SCAAP grant, 2003 September 4
    - CT DEP SCORP, 2004 September 7
    - CT Dept. of Labor, Workforce Investment Act, 2003
    - State of CT HUD grants, 2004
    - Connecticut Humanities Council grants, 2004
    - CT Dept. of Public Safety (2 folders), 2003
    - State of CT DOJ grants, 2003-2004
    - CT Rural Health, 2004-2005
    - Coastal Wine Groups (VADG program grant), 2002 August 8
    - COPS grants (DOJ), 2003, 2005
    - Connecticut Medical Examiners (DOJ), 2003 February 7
    - Creative Connections (DHHS Abstenience before marriage grant), 2003 January 21
    - CRERPA (DOC Info Central grant), 2002 September 20
    - CT River Valley Council of Elected Officials (CT Office of rural health), undated
    - CT Dept. of Public Health (DHHS), 2004 June 7
    - CT Dept. of Veterans Affairs, 2004 August 13
    - Coventry-Rural Development sewer system grant (USDA), undated
    - Crystal Lake Fire Dept. (Ellington, Assistance to Firefighters), 2004 April 12
    - Danielson Fire Dept. (EMS, Assistance to Firefighters, 2 folders), 2004
    - Durham Center Water Company (State DECD-CDBG funds), 2003 September 5
    - Durham Fire Dept. (FEMA), 2005 May 5
    - FEMA Snow removal emergency declaration, 2004 January 20
    - Fire Grant Press event, 2004 April 7
    - Fire prevention and safety grant, 2003 October 16
    - FEMA Assistance to Firefighters and awards (2 folders), 2003
    - Assistance to Firefighters, 2004
    - FEMA Snow removal, 2003
    - FEMA Assistance to Firefighters, 2002
  - Grant Files, Letters to the Editor, Issues, 1997-2005 (Box 147)
    - Family Lodge, 2004 September 12
    - Fire Act funding letter to chiefs, 2003 August 25
    - E. Brooklyn Volunteer Fire Dept. (Assistance to Firefighters), 2004 April 23
    - E. Great Plains Fire Co. (Norwich, Assistance to Firefighters)), 2004 April 9
    - Eastern CT REgional Education Services (EASTCONN) Headstart (US DHHS), 2004 March 19
    - EASTCONN Headstart (DHHS), 2004 September 16
    - East Haddam Volunteer Fire Dept (Assistance to Firefighters), 2004 April 1
    - Ellington CPS grant (DOJ), undated
    - Ellington Volunteer Fire Dept. (Assistance to Firefighters), 2004
    - Enfield Fire District 1 (Assistance to Firefighters), 2005 April 25
    - Enfield Fire Chiefs Association (FEMA Fire Safety grant), 2003 November 4
    - East Hampton Volunteer Fire Dept. (Assistance to Firefighters), 2004
    - ERASE (DOJ), 2002 September 26
    - EPA Norwich Brownfields, 2002 December 23
    - EPA East Hampton Brownfields, 2002 December 23
    - EPA Vernon Brownfields, 2002 February 5
    - EPA Brownfields grant, undated
    - EPA Sprague Brownfields, Baltic Mill, 2002 December 24
    - EPA New London Brownfields grant, 2002 December 4
    - FEMA Briefing, 2003 August 8
    - Fire Act letter to Fire Chiefs, 2003 August 25
    - First Hispanic Baptist Church, Rev. Daniel Martino (After School grants), undated
    - First Step, undated
    - Fish-N-Wheels (CT Counil on Developmental Disabilities), 2003 July 17
    - Planned Parenthood of CT, Inc., undated
    - Florence Griswold Museum (IMLS), 2003 September 23
    - Florence Griswold Museum (NEH), 2003-2004
    - Franklin Volunteer Fire Dept. (FEMA), 2003 April 7
    - Gardner Lake Volunteer Fire Dept., Salem (Assistance to Firefighters), 2004 April 16
    - Glastonbury Drug Free Communities, continuation (DOJ), 2004 August 20
    - Letters to the Editor (5 folders), 2005
    - Terrorism issues (2 folders), undated
    - Social Security (4 folders), undated
    - Newspaper clippings (2 folders), 1999-2006
    - Iraq, undated
    - Veterans issues, undated
    - Faith/Religion issues (2 folders), undated
    - Speeches, radio shows, editorial boards (3 folders), circa 2001
  - Long Island Sound, undated, 2005 (Box 148)
    - NURP, undated
    - Oysters, undated
    - GArbo Lobster, undated
    - Long Island Sound (LIS) Study Initiative, undated
    - LIS hearing, undated
    - Long Island Sound (7 folders), undated
    - LIS/Ambro (2 folders), undated
    - Long Island Sound study, undated
    - Long Island Sound Stewardship Act (2 folders), 2006
      - Bill summary and status
      - Language passed
      - Marine trades
      - Committee correspondence
      - Changes
      - Background
      - Press
      - Field hearing, 2005 June
      - Lise's notes
      - 108th
      - Related files
    - Environment, LISSA, 2004
    - Ambro, Bill Spicer, undated
    - Bob Ballard, undated
    - US EPA and US Army Corps of Engineers environmental impact statement, Final (2 folders), 2004 April
    - Appendices K and M, undated
  - LIS Hearing (H.R. 307) and Issue files I - P, undated, 2003-2005 (Box 149)
    - Subcommittee on Fisheries and Oceans, Legislative Field Hearing on HR 307, Long Island Sound Stewardship Act of 2005, 2005 June 25
    - LISSA Hearing logistics
    - LISSA drafts
      - I A - B
      - II A - B
      - III A - B
    - Cross Sound Cable
      - I - III
    - National Fish and Wildlife Foundation
    - Coastal Zone Management Program (CZMP)
    - Long Island Sound Study
    - LISRA Reauthorization
    - Dredging
      - I - II
    - International Children's Conference on the Environment, 2003
    - Keepers, undated
    - Labor, undated
    - Maritime ports, undated
    - Military events: Jordan, P.A., USMC, undated
    - Military issues: DPMO, POW/MIA, undated
    - Military issues: Military health issues, undated
    - Military issues: Military legislative issues, undated
    - Military issues: Army briefing, undated
    - Military issues: HUMMV Armor kits, undated
    - Monsanto file, undated
    - Multi cultural Roundtable, 2003
    - NECOG, undated
    - New England HIDTA Threat assessment, FY 2002, undated
    - NLDC, undated
    - Plum Island, undated
    - Postal service, undated
  - Issue files, Q - Z, undated, 1998-2005 (Box 150)
    - QSHC, undated, 1997-2001
      - Report to Congress, 1999
      - Appropriations Correspondence, 2001
      - Newsletters, undated
      - Management Plan, Action Plan, 1997-1998
      - Brochures, undated
      - Annual report, 1998-1999
      - Alliance of National Heritage Areas, undated
    - Quinnebaug Valley Community College, undated
    - Recommendations, undated
    - Seniors, undated
      - AARP, undated
      - Medicare, undated
      - Medicaid, undated
      - Government pension offset, undated
      - Ticket to work program, undated
      - CHOICES program, undated
      - Elderly outreach, undated
      - Local options for the Elderly, undated
      - SNET Retirees, undated
      - Senior Resources Agency on Aging, undated
    - Small Business: Small Business Administration, undated
    - Small Business: SCORE (floppy disk), undated
    - Social Security, undated
      - Women and Social security reform, undated
      - Notch issue, undated
      - SS disability--Doug Hopkins, undated
      - General, undated
      - 2nd district, undated
    - Social Services, undated
      - General, undated
      - TANF reauthorization, undated
      - Welfare, undated
    - Tourism, undated
      - Mystic area, undated
      - Lebanon, undated
      - Connecticut's Quiet Corner, undated
    - Trade: Travel--Israel trip, 2005
    - TRICARE information, undated
    - Trip reports: Taiwan, 2001 August 18
    - Trip reports: Iraq CODEL/DOD response, 2003 October 17-20
    - TUNZA Global Research International Children's Conference on the Environment, 2004
    - TVCCA, undated
    - Unions, undated
    - United Action, undated
    - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, undated
    - Workforce development, undated
      - Capital workforce partners, 2004-2005
      - Investment board (4 folders), 2002-2004
    - Veterans Casino LLC, undated
    - Volunteer Fire Fighters, undated
    - Welfare, undated
    - Women's issues, undated
  - Communications, 2006 (Box 151)
    - GSA Inventories, 2001-2006
    - Flag of the United States of America from Congressman Rob Simmons [to accompany flag?], undated
    - Email responses, 2000-2001
    - Jane (2 folders), 2006
    - Jeff, 2005-2006
    - Rob (2 folders), 1999-2006
    - Newspapers, 2001-2002
    - Leave requests (19 folders), 2001-2006
    - Bucked letters (2 folders), 2006
    - Out of District (2 folders), 2005-2006
    - State Issues, 2003-2004, 2006
    - Correspondence (2 folders), 2006 October - December
  - Vietnam Caucus/Committee, Defense review, undated, 2004-2006 (Box 153)
    - Vietnam Trade Council, undated
    - Dr. Pham Hong Son, undated
    - Vietnam (I-IV), undated; [4 ff]
    - Vietnam PNTR, undated
    - Vietnam POW/MIA (I-II), undated; [2 ff]
    - U.S.-Vietnam Caucus (I-II), undated; [2 ff]
    - DPMO, undated
    - POW/MIA Joint Task Force Full Accounting, undated
    - Vietnam Human Rights, undated
    - Committee Defense Review (CDR, I-IV), undated; [4 ff]
    - Regional Powers Panel (I-III), undated; [3 ff]
    - Open Source Intelligence (OSINT), undated
    - OSINT/Information sharing, undated
    - OSINT/MOSAEC, undated
    - OSINT Conference, 2006 February
    - OSINT: Simmons amendment to HR 10, undated
    - OSINT: 9-11 Commission/HR 10 markup, 2004 September 29
    - OSINT: 9-11 Report, undated
  - Committee Defense Review (CDR), Labor, Grants, Indians, undated, 2004-2006 (Box 154)
    - HR 10 (I-II), undated; [2 ff]
    - OSINT (II-IV), undated; [3 ff]
    - Peace Alliance (SB 1756/HB 3760), undated
    - ATU Speech, undated
    - NAGE, undated
    - NTEU, undated
    - Right to Work, undated
    - AFL-CIO, undated
    - APWU, undated
    - Endorsements, undated
    - FEW, undated
    - UAW, undated
    - Labor exit memo, undated
    - Rail, undated
    - Marine Engineers Riding gangs, undated
    - EB, undated
    - ICWU, undated
    - FAA/NATCA meeting, 2006 January 31
    - Pensions, undated
    - Airline pilots, undated
    - Flight attendants, undated
    - Labor (general), undated
    - Department of Labor, undated
    - Labor, undated
    - LIUNA, undated
    - MSHA, undated
    - Disability, undated
    - Right to organize, undated
    - Boilermakers, undated
    - AFSCME, undated
    - Metal trades, undated
    - Steel workers, undated
    - SEIU, undated
    - Teamsters, undated
    - Asnuntuck Community College, undated
    - OSHA, undated
    - Speech to Metal trades, undated
    - Labor forum, 2005 August 16
    - Machinists, undated
    - Route 11, undated
    - Labor meeting, 2004 January 26
    - Labor thank you leeters and associated issues (I-II), undated; [2 ff]
    - Submarine trade press, 2006 February 20 - March 6
    - AFGE (I-II), undated; [2 ff]
    - Grants, undated
    - BIA decision, undated
    - BIA Pequot, undated
    - Indians, undated
    - Non-Gaming/Lobbying Indian affairs, undated
    - Common Sense Indian Gambling Reform Act and Lobbying, undated
  - Coast Guard, Transportation, Subject Files (Tourism-Veterans ), undated, 1995-2002 (Box 155)
    - Coast Guard, undated, 2002
      - Academy and sexual assault; an overview of cases and policy, undated
      - Congressional Board of Visitors orientation binders (I-III_, 2002
    - Transportation, undated
      - Step-Ons, undated
      - Federal highways, undated
      - HR 3550 substitute (I-IV), undated
      - HR 3, Transportation Equity Act (I-II), undated
      - Railroads, undated
    - Subject Files, undated, 1995-1998
      - Tourism taxes, 1998
      - Tourism Task Force, 1996
      - Tourism--SEC (I-II), undated
      - Tourism--NCSL, undated
      - Tourism impact, 1995
      - Transportation Task Force, undated
      - Turek Bridge, undated
      - Uncas on Thamas, undated
      - UConn, undated
      - Urban issues (I-II), undated
      - Vessel Fuel tax, undated
      - Vessel taxes, undated
      - Vets--Electric, undated
      - Veterans issues, undated
  - Subject Files (Visiting Nurses - Youth Issues), Press releases, Legislative Activities, undated, 1991-1999 (Box 156)
    - Visiting nurses, undated
    - Volunteer immunity, undated
    - Waste water tax credit, HR 5339, undated
    - Welcome centers/Tourism, undated
    - Westerly Water I- III (3 folders), undated
    - Westerly Water/Pawcatuck, undated
    - White Rock Bridge, undated
    - Winery Shippers, undated
    - Yardney, undated
    - Youth issues, undated
    - Press releases/Media, undated
    - Legislative Activity, undated
      - Legislation, 1991
      - Legislation (I-III), 1992
      - Legislative Proposals, 1993